Gentlemen?
HOWARD: Why couldn't you have
just done what Leonard did...
(Howard:)...and get Penny a new boyfriend?
(Leonard:)My leg is killing me. Thanks for asking.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Leonard:)Okay, I have just one question for you.
(Leonard:)While I am perfectly happy
with the way things are...
...you said that you didn't wanna go out
with me because I was too smart for you.
Well, news flash, lady:
David Underhill is 10 times smarter than me.
(Leonard:)You'd have to drive a railroad spike into
his brain for me to beat him at checkers.
Next to him, I'm one of those sign-language
gorillas who knows how to ask for grapes.
(Leonard:)So my question is...
(Leonard:)...what's up with that?